Guide to the Brooklyn playbills and programs collection BCMS.0041
Brooklyn Collection
- Montauk Theatre
  - The Merchant of Venice, December 21, 1903 (Box 2)
    Henry Irving and His Company in Shakespeare's Comedy, "The Merchant of Venice." With Henry Irving, Gerald Lawrence, W. Farren Jr., Laurence Irving, F. Tyars et al. Also, Casimir Delavigne's "Louis XI" adapted by Dion Boucicault.
  - Dante, December 21, 1903 (Box 2)
    Henry Irving and His Company in "Dante." By Mm. Sardou and Moreau. Rendered into English by Laurence Irving. With Henry Irving, Gerald Lawrence, William Mollison, Laurence Irving, Frank Tyars et al.
  - Cousin Kate, January 4, 1904 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Ethel Barrymore in "Cousin Kate" by Hubert Henry Davies. Also with Bruce McRae, Grant Stewart, Harold Grau, Annie Adams, Beatrice Agnew, Doris Rankin.
  - Parsifal, January 9, 1904 (Box 2)
    Henry W. Savage presents Richard Wagner's play, "Parsifal." With Walter H. Rothwell, Mme. Kirby Lunn, Francis Maclennan et al.
  - The Office Boy, January 11, 1904 (Box 2)
    Frank Daniels in "The Office Boy." A Musical Comedy in Two Acts. Libretto by Harry B. Smith. Composed by Ludwig Englander. From the French of Maurice Ordonneau and Paul Gavault. Also with Alfred Hickman, Sydney Toler, Gilbert Clayton et al.
  - The Pretty Sister of Jose, January 18, 1904 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Maude Adams in "The Pretty Sister of Jose." By Mrs. Frances Hodgson Burnett. Also with Henry Ainley, G. Harrison Hunter, Edgar Selwyn, Joseph Francoeur, Francis Byrne et al.
  - The Man from Blankleys, January 25, 1904 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Charles Hawtrey in the Comedy, "The Man from Blankleys." By F. Anstey. Also with Fred Thorne, Wm. F. Owen, E. A. Plumpton, Holman Clark et al.
  - The Girl With The Green Eyes, March 14, 1904 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents the play, "The Girl With The Green Eyes." By Clyde Fitch. Featuring Clara Bloodgood. Also with Wm. H. Tooker, Grace Henderson, Frank Dekum, Edith Taliaferro, Rose Flynn et al.
  - Nancy Brown, March 21, 1904 (Box 2)
    Daniel V. Arthur presents Marie Cahill in, the Musical Comedy, "Nancy Brown." Book by George H. Broadhurst and Frederic Ranken. Music Cole & Johnson Bros. and Silvio S. Hein. Staged by John Hyams. Also with H. W. Tredenick, Julius Steger et al.
  - Glittering Gloria, April 11, 1904 (Box 2)
    John C. Fisher and Thos. W. Ryley present "Glittering Gloria." A Comedy with Music. Written by Hugh Morton; Music by Bernard Holt. With Cyril Scott, Percy F. Ames, Ferdinand Gottschalk, Forest Robinson et al.
  - The Proud Prince, April 25, 1904 (Box 2)
    E. H. Sothern in "The Proud Prince." A Miracle Play by Justin Huntly McCarthy, author of "If I Were King." Also with Orme Caldara, John Findlay, Rowland Buckstone, Malcolm Bradley et al.
  - Ranson's Folly, May 2, 1904 (Box 2)
    Robert Edeson in the Comedy of American Army Life, "Ranson's Folly." By Richard Harding Davis. Also with Ada Curry, Joseph Hughes, Grace Lespiel, Richard Sterling et al.
  - The Dictator, September 19, 1904 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents William Collier in "The Dictator." A Farce, in Three Acts, by Richard Harding Davis. Also with Charles Jackson, John Barrymore, George Nash, Thomas McGrath et al. Stage Direction, William Seymour.
  - The Maid and the Mummy, October 3, 1904 (Box 2)
    Carle Amusement Company presents "The Maid and the Mummy." A Musical Melange in Two Acts. Book and lyrics by Richard Carle; Music by Robert Hood Bowers; Managing Director, Chas. Marks. With Richard F. Carroll, Edward Garvie, Geo. A. Beane et al.
  - Lohengrin, October 10, 1904 (Box 2)
    Henry W. Savage presents the English Grand Opera Co. and Full Grand Opera Orchestra. Conductors: N. B. Emanuel and Elliott Schenck. "Lohengrin" and "Tannhauser" by Richard Wagner, "I Pagliacci" by R. Leoncavallo, "Cavalleria Rusticana by Pietro Mascagni.
  - The Sorceress, November 21, 1904 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents "The Sorceress." A play by Victorien Sardou. Translated by Louis N. Parker. With Mrs. Patrick Campbell, Frederick Perry, Guy Standing, George Riddell, L. Rogers Lytton et al. Stage Direction: William Seymour.
  - Love's Lottery, December 19, 1904 (Box 2)
    F. C. Whitney presents Mme. Schumann-Heink in "Love's Lottery." Libretto by Stanislau Stange; Music by Julian Edwards. Also with H. W. TreDenick, George L. Tallman, W. H. Thompson, Louise Gunning, Delight Barsch et al.
  - A Madcap Princess, December 26, 1904 (Box 2)
    Charles B. Dillingham presents Lulu Glaser in, the Comic Opera, "A Madcap Princess." Based on "When Knighthood Was in Flower"by Charles Major. Music: Ludwig Englander; Libretto: Harry B. Smith. Also with William Pruette, Bertram Wallis et al.
  - Letty, January 16, 1905 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents William Faversham in "Letty." A Drama in Four Acts and an Epilogue, by Arthur W. Pinero. Also with Ivo Dawson, Frank Goldsmith, Arthur Playfair, Fritz Williams, Tom Terriss et al.
  - The School Girl, January 23, 1905 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Edna May in the Musical, "The School Girl." By Paul M. Potter and Henry Hamilton. Music by Leslie Stuart; Lyrics by Chas. H. Taylor. Also with Mildred Baker, Mrs. J. P. West, Lulu Valli et al.
  - The Usurper, February 6, 1905 (Box 2)
    N. C. Goodwin presents "The Usurper." A Comedy-Drama by I. N. Morris. Direction: George J. Appleton. With N. C. Goodwin, Norman Tharp, Eille Norwood, Felix Edwardes, W. H. Post et al.
  - Little Johnny Jones (The American Jockey), February 20, 1905 (Box 2)
    Sam H. Harris presents, The Yankee Doodle Comedian, George M. Cohan in the Musical, "Little Johnny Jones (The American Jockey)." Also with Jerry J. Cohan, J. Bernard Dyllyn, Sam J. Ryan, Donald Brian et al.
  - Business is Business, March 27, 1905 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents William H. Crane in the Comedy-Drama, "Business is Business." By Octave Mirbeau. Tanslated by Robert Hichens. Also with H. Hassard Short, George Backus, Sheridan Block, Walter Hale, et al.
  - Woodland, April 3, 1905 (Box 2)
    Henry W. Savage presents the Musical Fantasy "Woodland." Book and Lyrics by Frank Pixley. Music by Gustav Luders. Staged by George Marion. With Charles Dow Clark, Louize Tozier, Harry Bulger, Douglas Ruthven et al.
  - The Little Minister, April 10, 1905 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Miss Maude Adams, in the Comedy, "The Little Minister." By J. M. Barrie. Also with Arthur Byron, Eugene Jepson, George Irving, Lloyd Carleton et al.
  - King Richard III, April 24, 1905 (Box 2)
    Richard Mansfield and His Company in Shakespeare's Tragedy, "King Richard III." With A. G. Andrews, Mildred Morris, Leona Powers, Richard Mansfield, Leslie Kenyon et al. Also "The Misanthrope" by Moliere and "Ivan the Terrible" by Tolstoi.
  - Fatinitza, May 1, 1905 (Box 2)
    Charles B. Dillingham presents Fritzi Scheff in "Fatinitza." A Comic Opera by Franz von Suppe. Also with Arthur Cunningham, Louise Le Baron, Louis Harrison et al. Also, "Boccaccio" by Franz von Suppe.
  - The Fascinating Mr. Vanderveldt, March 19, [1906] (Box 2)
    Miss Ellis Jeffreys in "The Fascinating Mr. Vanderveldt." By Alfred Sutro. Stage Direction, Charles Cartwright. With Frank Worthing, Ruby Bridges, Lena Halliday et al. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
  - The Show Shop, October 18, 1915 (Box 2)
    Selwyn & Company present "The Show Shop" by James Forbes, author of "The Chorus Lady." With George Sidney, Zelda Sears, Dolly Lewis, Walter Young, Robert Frazer et al.
  - Daddy Long Legs, February 28, 1916 (Box 2)
    "Daddy Long Legs," a Comedy by Jean Webster. Henry Miller, Manager. With Byron Beasley, A. Hylton Allen, Ray Brown, Robert Waters, Edward Howard et al.
  - Erstwhile Susan, December 4, 1916 (Box 2)
    Madison Corey & Joseph Riter present Mrs. Fiske in the Comedy, "Erstwhile Susan." By Marian de Forest, based on "Barnabetta" by Helen R. Martin. Also with Walter Wilson, Robert Stowe Gill, Rikel Kent, John Daly Murphy, Henry Mortimer et al.
  - Fair and Warmer, December 25, 1916 (Box 2)
    Selwyn & Company present "Fair and Warmer" with Madge Kennedy. A play by Avery Hopwood, author of "Seven Days." Also with John Arthur, Ethel Wilson, Robert Ober et al.
  - Seven Chances, January 22, 1917 (Box 2)
    David Belasco presents "Seven Chances" by Roi Cooper Megrue. With Frank Craven, John Butler, Hayward Ginn, Charles Brokate, Frank Morgan, Harry Leighton, Freeman Wood et al.
  - The Yellow Jacket, March 5, 1917 (Box 2)
    Mr. and Mrs. Coburn present "The Yellow Jacket." A play by George C. Hazelton and Benrimo. Music by William Furst. With Thomas E. Jackson, Mr. Coburn, Howard Kyle, Lillian Spencer, Beatrice Prentice et al.
  - The Country Cousin, January 14, 1918 (Box 2)
    Klaw & Erlanger and George C. Tyler present Alexandra Carlisle in "The Country Cousin." By Booth Tarkington and Julian Street. Staged by Robert Milton. Also with Julia Stuart, Beatrice Noyes, Donald Gallaher et al.
  - The Auctioneer, January 13, 1919 (Box 2)
    David Belasco presents David Warfield in "The Auctioneer," a comedy in Three Acts. Also with Ida Grooper, Marie Bates, Louis Hendricks, Harry Lewellyn, Helena Phillips et al. Stage Manager, William Boag.
  - Daddies, February 9, 1920 (Box 2)
    David Belasco presents "Daddies." A Comedy in Four Acts by John L. Hobble. With Charles Hammond, John W. Cope, Herbert Fortier, George Abbott, S. K. Walker, Claude Brooke et al.
  - One Night in Rome, March 8, 1920 (Box 2)
    Laurette Taylor in "One Night in Rome," by J. Hartley Manners. With Philip Merivale, H. Cooper Cliffe, George Majeroni, Barry Baxter et al.
  - The Storm, August 30, 1920 (Box 2)
    George Broadhurst presents "The Storm." A Melodrama by Langdon McCormick. Staged by Lillian Trimble Bradley. With Ben Taggart, Eric Maxon, Charles Henderson, Joseph Driscoll, Katherine Hayden et al.
  - Clarence, September 13, 1920 (Box 2)
    Booth Tarkington's Comedy, "Clarence." Staged by Frederick Stanhope. With Alfred Lunt, Agnes Findlay, Barlow Borland, William Lorenz et al.
  - Captain Applejack, March 19, [1923] (Box 2)
    Sam H. Harris' "Captain Applejack" by Walter Hackett. With Wallace Eddinger and Mary Nash. Staged by Author and Sam Forrest. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
  - Weeds, March 16, 1925 (Box 2)
    Samuel Wallach presents "Weeds." A Comedy-Drama in Three Acts and a Prologue. By John B. Hymer and Leroy Clemens. Staged by Priestly Morrison. With Leo Kennedy, Berton Churchill, Clyde Veaux et al.
- Nassau Theatre
  - Wine, Woman and Song, April 17, 1905 (Box 2)
    Performances: M. M. Theise's Own Company "Wine, Woman and Song."; "What Married Men Do" by Chas. Nichols; Raymond and Clayton; Four Mistletoe Girls; Bonita; Woods and Bohm; The Toreador Trio in "Hop Fiend Bill"; and others.
  - The Jolly Girls Extravaganza Company, September 11, 1905 (Box 2)
    Performances: The Jolly Girls Extravaganza Co.; "A Tempest in a Tea House"; Bigger and Lancaster; Prof. W. M. Bristol's Equine Wonders; Lassaro Bros.; Geo. T. Davis; "An Honest Politician"; and more.
  - A Bohemian Beauty, September 18, 1905 (Box 2)
    Tom Miner's Bohemian Burlesquers in "A Bohemian Beauty" by George Totten Smith. Staged by Tom Miner and Barney Gerard. With Will H. Ward, Andy Gardner, Grace Tremont, Ida Nicolai et al.
- National
  - Swing Time, November 8-17, [c. 1936] (Box 2)
    Screenings: "Swing Time" with Fred Astaire, Ginger Rogers; "They Met in a Taxi" with Fay Wray; "Down to the Sea" with Ben Lyon; "Passione Siciliana"; "My American Wife" with Ann Sothern; "7 Sinners" with Edmund Lowe; and more.
- New Brighton Theatre
  - [Various performances], June 3, 1912 (Box 2)
    Robert Recker's New Brighton Orchestra; Connie Francis; Romalo and Delano; Carl McCullough; The Huntings in "The Fool House"; Joseph E. Howard and Mabel McCane; Winslow and Stryker; and others.
  - [Various performances], July 5, 1915 (Box 2)
    New Brighton Theatre Orchestra; Schreck and Percival; Jean Chalion; Geo. Howell and Associate Players in "The Red Fox Trot"; Ned Monroe and Keller Mack; Cecil Lean; and others.
  - [Various performances], June 18, 1917 (Box 2)
    Performances: New Brighton Theatre Orchestra; Eddy Duo; Martin Brennan and Ethel Powell; Ray and Gordon Dooley; Linne's Classic Dancers; Rockwell and Wood; "Rubeville" featuring Harry B. Watson and Jere Delaney; and others.
  - [Various performances], May 19, 1924 (Box 2)
    Performances: New Brighton Theatre Orchestra; News Views; Bordner and Boyer; McCarthy Sisters; McKay and Ardine in "The Night Watchman"; Frank Hurst and Eddie Vogt; Hackett and Delmar in "Dance Madness"; and others.
- New Montauk Theatre
  - The Duchess of Dantzic [2 items - one souvenir program and one regular program], September 25, 1905 (Box 2)
    Klaw & Erlanger present George Edwardes' London Lyric Theatre Company in "The Duchess of Dantzic." Book and Lyrics by Henry Hamilton. Music by Ivan Caryll. With Evie Greene, Lottie Sargent, Frank Greene et al.
  - The Pearl and the Pumpkin, November 6, 1905 (Box 2)
    Klaw & Erlanger's production of "The Pearl and the Pumpkin." Book by Paul West and W. W. Denslow. Lyrics by Paul West. Music by John W. Bratton. Stage Direction, Herbert Gresham and Ned Wayburn. With Gertie Carlisle, Taylor Granville et al.
  - Her Great Match, January 22, 1906 (Box 2)
    Charles Dillingham presents Maxine Elliott in "Her Great Match." A Play, in Four Acts, by Clyde Fitch. Also with Madge Girdlestone, Nellie Thorne, Mme. Mathilde Cottrelly, Suzanne Perry, Charles Cherry, Herbert Standing et al.
  - The Toast of the Town, February 26, 1906 (Box 2)
    Viola Allen in "The Toast of the Town." A Play, in Four Acts, by Clyde Fitch. Also with Isabel Irving, Fanny Addison Pitt, Alice Wilson, Conway Tearle, Harrison Hunter et al.
  - The Fascinating Mr. Vanderveldt, March 19, 1906 (Box 2)
    Miss Ellis Jeffreys in "The Fascinating Mr. Vanderveldt." By Alfred Sutro. Also with Frank Worthing, Ruby Bridges, Lena Halliday, Essex Dane, Muriel Wylford, Constance Walton et al.
  - Just Out of College, March 26, 1906 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Joseph Wheelock, Jr. in "Just Out of College." A Comedy by George Ade. Also with Eugene Jepson, Charles Jackson, George Henry Trader et al.
  - The Ham Tree, April 2, 1906 (Box 2)
    Klaw & Erlanger's production for McIntyre and Heath in the Musical Vaudeville, "The Ham Tree." Book by George V. Hobart. Lyric and Music by Wm. Jerome and Jean Schwartz. Staged by Herbert Gresham and Ned Wayburn. With James McIntyre, T. K. Heath, et al.
  - Strongheart, April 9, 1906 (Box 2)
    Robert Edeson in, the Comedy-Drama, "Strongheart" by William C. De Mille. Also with Harrison Ford, Richard Sterling, H. David Todd, Sydney Ainsworth, F. A. Turner, Francis Bonn et al.
  - The Embassy Ball, April 23, 1906 (Box 2)
    Daniel Frohman presents Lawrance D'Orsay in "The Embassy Ball." A Comedy by Augustus Thomas, author of "On the Quiet," etc. Also with George Clarke, Forrest Robinson, Walter Hitchcock, Harold Heaton, George Grimes et al.
  - Magda, April 30, 1906 (Box 2)
    Miss Nance O'Neil in Sudermann's Play, "Magda." Direction of Mr. McKee Rankin. Also with Claire Washington, Clara Thompson, Lawrence Griffith, Andrew Robson et al. Also Sudermann's "Fires of St. John," Ibsen's "Hedda Gabler" and "Rosmersholm."
  - The Belle of Mayfair, September 16, 1907 (Box 2)
    Thomas W. Ryley Production of "The Belle of Mayfair." By Charles H. E. Brookfield and Cosmo Hamilton. Music by Leslie Stuart. With Fred Rivenhall, Harry B. Burcher, Charles J. Stine, John Ardizone, Fletcher Norton et al.
  - Lola From Berlin, October 21, 1907 (Box 2)
    Klaw & Erlanger present Miss Lulu Glaser and Company, including Ralph C. Herz, in "Lola From Berlin." A Comedy by John J. McNally. Lyrics and Music by William Jerome and Jean Schwartz. Staged by Al Holbrook. Also George Le Guere, Minnette Barrett, et al.
  - The Rich Mr. Hoggenheimer, October 28, 1907 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Sam Bernard in "The Rich Mr. Hoggenheimer." Book and Lyrics by Harry B. Smith. Music by Ludwig Englander. Staged by Ben Teal. Also with Mortimer H. Weldon, David Torrence et al.
  - The Straight Road, November 4, 1907 (Box 2)
    Wagenhals & Kemper present Blanche Walsh in "The Straight Road." A Play, in Four Acts, by Clyde Fitch. Also with Alma Kruger, Ina Brooks, Jessie Ralph, Jean Patriquin, Lizzie Colter et al.
  - Anna Karenina, November 11, 1907 (Box 2)
    Sam S. and Lee Shubert (Inc.) offer Virginia Harned in "Anna Karenina." Based on the novel by Tolstoi [Tolstoy]. By Edmond Guiraud. Adapted by Thomas W. Broadhurst. Also with Andrew Robson, Foster Williams, Robert Warwick et al.
  - The Fool Hath Said, "There Is No God.", December 2, 1907 (Box 2)
    E.H. Sothern presents "The Fool Hath Said, 'There Is No God.'" A Play based on Dostoieffski's [Dostoyevsky's], "Crime and Punishment." By Laurence Irving. Direction of Lee Shubert. With Albert S. Howson, Sydney Mather, Katherine Wilson et al.
  - Brewster's Millions, December 16, 1907 (Box 2)
    Frederic Thompson presents Edward Abeles and Company in "Brewster's Millions." By George Barr McCutcheon. Dramatized by Winchell Smith and Byron Ongley. With Sumner Gard, Joseph Woodburn, Willard Howe, Leslie Bassett, Emily Lytton et al.
  - The Little Cherub, December 23, 1907 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Hattie Williams in Owen Hall's Musical Comedy, "The Little Cherub." Music by Ivan Caryll. Staged by Ben Teal. Also with Henry V. Donnelly, Alden MacClaskie, James Blakeley, Will West et al.
  - The Chorus Lady, February 24, 1908 (Box 2)
    Rose Stahl in "The Chorus Lady." A Four-Act Comedy by James Forbes. Also with Alice Leigh, Eva Dennison, Frederick Schoekel, Thos. Maguire, Giles Shine, Francis Byrne et al. Staged by Mr. Forbes.
  - The Morals of Marcus, March 9, 1908 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Marie Doro in "The Morals of Marcus." A Comedy by W. J. Locke. Also with C. Aubrey Smith, Hubert Harben, Forrest Robinson, William Evans, Alexander King, Jr., Beatrice Forbes-Robertson et al.
  - Her Sister, March 16, 1908 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Ethel Barrymore in "Her Sister." By Clyde Fitch and Cosmo Gordon Lennox. Also with Fanny Addison Pitt, Lucile Watson, Desmond Kelley, Louise Drew, Anita Rothe et al.
  - The Jesters, April 6, 1908 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents Maude Adams in "The Jesters." Translated from the French of Miguel Zamacois. By John Raphael. Also with Mathilde Cottrelly, Consuelo Bailey, Fred Tyler et al.
  - The Soul Kiss, October 12, 1908 (Box 2)
    F. Ziegfeld Jr's, "The Soul Kiss." Book and Lyrics by Harry B. Smith. Music by Maurice Levi. Staged by Herbert Gresham and Julian Mitchell. With Adeline Genee, Mortimer H. Weldon, Amelia Rose, Vera Michelena et al.
  - The Girl Behind the Counter, December 7, 1908 (Box 2)
    Sam S. and Lee Shubert (Inc.) and Lew Fields present, Lew Fields in the Musical Comedy, "The Girl Behind the Counter." Book by Leedham Bantock and Arthur Anderson. Music by Howard Talbot. Also with Connie Ediss, Pearl Lund et al.
  - The Honor of the Family, December 14, 1908 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents, Otis Skinner in, "The Honor of the Family." A play, in Four Acts, after Balzac, by Emile Fabre. Adapted by Paul M. Potter. Also with A. G. Andrews, Francis Carlyle, Harry Burkhardt, Russell Crauford et al.
  - In the Glade of the Orchids, January 4, 1909 (Box 2)
    Cohan and Harris Minstrels with George Evans and 100 Honey Boys presenting an Entertainment embracing Minstrelsy, Vaudeville, Burlesque and Musical Comedy commencing with, "In the Glade of the Orchids."
  - The Yankee Prince, February 8, 1909 (Box 2)
    George M. Cohan and His Royal Family in, His Latest Musical Play, "The Yankee Prince." Direction of Cohan and Harris. With Jerry J. Cohan, George M. Cohan, George Parsons, Frank Hollins et al.
  - The Bachelor's Baby, November 13, 1911 (Box 2)
    Charles Frohman presents, Francis Wilson in the Comedy Farce, "The Bachelor's Baby." By Francis Wilson. Also with Louis Massen, Richard Gordon, Thomas F. Tracy, E. Soldene Powell et al.
  - Maggie Pepper, January 15, 1912 (Box 2)
    Henry B. Harris presents Rose Stahl in "Maggie Pepper." By Charles Klein, author of "The Lion and the Mouse," "The Third Degree," etc. Also with Agnes Marc, Gretchen Lang, Lee Kohlmar, Eleanor Lawson et al.
  - The Case of Becky, December 23, 1912 (Box 2)
    David Belasco presents, Francis Starr in, "The Case of Becky." A Play in Three Acts by Edward Locke. Also with Albert Bruning, Harry C. Browne, Eugene O'Brien, Charles Dalton, John P. Brawn et al.
  - The Highway of Life, November 16, 1914 (Box 2)
    "The Highway of Life," a dramatic version, by Louis N. Parker, of "David Copperfield" by Charles Dickens. With J. V. Bryant, Eva Vincent, Prince Miller, Rhoda Beresford et al.
- Novelty Theatre
  - My Partner, [January 17, 1889] (Box 2)
    "My Partner" by Bartley Campbell, Esq. Stage Manager, P. J. Reynolds. With D. Gilfether, P. J. Reynolds, Charles Willard, Charles Ray, William Hamilton, James M. Martin et al.
  - Casper, The Yodler, February 16, 1891 (Box 2)
    Charles T. Ellis in, the Musical Comedy-Drama, "Casper, The Yodler." By William Carlton. Also with Frank E. Jamison, James F. Tighe, Charles F. McCarthy et al.
  - Managerial Troubles, October 9, 1899 (Box 2)
    Performances: Jones and Sutton; Howard Thurston; Madeline Marshall & Lizette Darling; Caicedo; Joe Linder; Idalene Cotton and Nick Long in "Managerial Troubles"; Haines and Pettingill; and others.
  - Two Girls and One Man, December 11, 1899 (Box 2)
    Performances: Overture - Happy Days; Baldwin and Daly; Dick and Alice McAvoy; Gallando; Master George Bly; Miss Lizzie Evans and Co. in "Two Girls and One Man"; Tom Mack; Joe Welch; and others.
  - The Soubrette and the Cop, January 29, 1900 (Box 2)
    Performances: Overture - Medley; The Harpers; Drawee; Eddie Girard, assisted by Jessie Gardner, in "The Soubrette and the Cop"; Irene and Zaza; Keough and Ballard; and others.
  - Their First Quarrel, February 26, 1900 (Box 2)
    Performances: Harry and Sadie Fields; Smith Doty and Coe; Edgar Foreman & Julia West in "Their First Quarrel," Marion Russell and Co., Carrie Graham, and others.
  - The Musketeers, March 12, 1900 (Box 2)
    Performances: Overture; The Tennis Trio; Jack Norworth; Carrington, Holland & Galpin; Jessie Millar; Paul Gilmore in "The Musketeers"; Louise Dresser; and others.
  - The Secret, April 16, 1900 (Box 2)
    Performances: Operatic Selection; The Craigs; Eddie Leonard; Nelson and Milledge in "The Secret"; Lotta Gladstone; The Girl With The Auburn Hair; Tom Mack; Three Sa-Vans; John C. Fox and Katie Allen in "The Flat Next Door"; and others.
- Orpheum Theatre
  - The Yellow Dragon, January 9, 1905 (Box 2)
    Performances: Louis Reinhard's Orpheum Orchestra; Marlo and Aldo; The Village Choir; Mr. and Mrs. Sidney Drew in, "The Yellow Dragon," by George R. Deane.
  - The Land of Two Moons, February 13, 1905 (Box 2)
    Refinded Vaudeville. Performances: Louis Reinhard's Orchestra; Lavine and Leonard; T. W. Eckert and Emma Berg in, the operetta by W. W. Prosser, "The Land of Two Moons."
  - An Ancient Roman, September 18, 1905 (Box 2)
    Refinded Vaudeville. Performances: Louis C. A. Reinhard's Orchestra; The Larsen Sisters; Cooper and Robinson; Jules and Ella Garrison in "An Ancient Roman"; Winona Winters.
  - Refinded Vaudeville, October 2, 1905 (Box 2)
    Performances: Louis C.A. Reinhard's Orchestra; Johnson and Wells; Mabelle Adams; Ed. F. Reynard; The Empire City Quartette.
  - Vaudeville Performances, November 5, 1905 (Box 2)